<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 
          This file is protected by Copyright. Please refer to the COPYRIGHT file distributed with this 
               source distribution.

This file is part of REDHAWK Basic Components DataConverter.

REDHAWK Basic Components DataConverter is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of 
the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either 
version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

REDHAWK Basic Components DataConverter is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; 
without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR 
PURPOSE.  See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License along with this 
program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.
-->
<!DOCTYPE softpkg PUBLIC "-//JTRS//DTD SCA V2.2.2 SPD//EN" "softpkg.dtd">
<softpkg id="DCE:dfaf2978-cb89-49a9-8c4e-a8e15382fcdd" name="BurstDeserializer" type="sca_compliant">
  <title></title>
  <author>
    <name>null</name>
  </author>
  <description>BurstDeserializer demuxes framed data into seperate unfrmaed output streams.   

Framed data can be visualized as a matrix.  The sri.subsize determines the rows of the matrix, which are associated with the &quot;x&quot; direction.  The columns are associated with the &quot;y&quot; direction.  This yields the following equation which should hold for framed data:

numFrames= pktSize/sri.subsize;

numFrames is the number of rows of the matrix, and sri.subsize is the number of columns in the matrix.  

If the transpose property is set to true, the burst delimeter outputs one stream per column.  Thus, each packet yields sri.subsize unique output streams.  If transpose is set to false, the burst delimeter outputs one stream per row. Thus, each packet yields numFrames unique outputStreams.

Because the pktSize can change from packetToPacket, the number of output streams can also change per packet when transpose is set to false.  Thus, the BurstDeserializer is designed so that each frame of each packet becomes a unique streamID when transpose is set to false.

When transpose is set to true, the newStreams are created only when the subsize changes.  This is the typical use case for steady-state processing in most real-time systems.</description>
  <propertyfile type="PRF">
    <localfile name="BurstDeserializer.prf.xml"/>
  </propertyfile>
  <descriptor>
    <localfile name="BurstDeserializer.scd.xml"/>
  </descriptor>
  <implementation id="cpp">
    <description>The implementation contains descriptive information about the template for a software component.</description>
    <code type="Executable">
      <localfile name="cpp/BurstDeserializer"/>
      <entrypoint>cpp/BurstDeserializer</entrypoint>
    </code>
    <compiler name="/usr/bin/gcc" version="4.1.2"/>
    <programminglanguage name="C++"/>
    <humanlanguage name="EN"/>
    <os name="Linux"/>
    <processor name="x86"/>
    <processor name="x86_64"/>
  </implementation>
</softpkg>
